

SHUBHAM RANI

Software Developer

I am a competent web developer with 3 year of solid work experience in designing and developing websites for agency clients. I am a creative person who can produce websites from concept to launch. my websites are optimised to load fast, be responsive and be a pleasure to use. I have worked effectively both independently and as part of a team, and I am capable of being highly productive either way.

<u>shubhamrani555@gmail.com</u>

+91 6263699865

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/shubham-rani-89b75a257

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer SMD Web Tech Pvt Ltd November 2023 – Present

Responsibilities

- Responsible for working on HTML Templates.
- Responsible for coding on HTML.
- Responsible for coding on CSS.
- Responsible for coding on Bootstrap.
- Responsible for coding on JavaScript.
- Responsible for coding on Laravel.

Systems Engineer
Infosys Limited
March 2022 - October

March 2022 - October 2023

Responsibilities

- Responsible for coding on Bootstrap.
- Responsible for coding on JavaScript.
- Responsible for working on HTML Templates.
- Responsible for HTML email development
- Responsible for coding on CSS.

CERTIFICATES

- Infosys Certified Front End Web Developer
- Infosys Certified MySQL Associate
- Infosys Certified PL/SQL Associate
- Infosys Certified AWA Cloud Practitioner
- Infosys Certified CPQ Developer
- IBM Plum Certification

EXTRA CURRICULUM ACTIVITIES

CSR (Corporate Social Responsibilities) Activities in Infosys

- Establishes Library set up at---Bhagwati
 High School and Sweet life Ideal Education
 Niketan.
- Volunteer at cyber security event organised by Odisha police.

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- Angular
- Laravel
- MySQL
- PHP
- Git
- Agile Mindset
- Good Communication

PROJECTS

- https://lubypay.com/
- https://ticktappay.com/
- https://www.hisaka.co.jp/english/
- https://bonaireisland.com/experiences/sights eeing/sites/isidel-beach-park/

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering Trinity Institute of Technology & Research College, Bhopal

2016 - 2020

Intermediate (10+2)

S.R.R.S Senior Secondary School, Patna Bihar 2014 – 2016

Matriculation (10) S.R.R.S High School, Bihar 2013

INTERESTS

Travelling, Net Surfing, Games, Cooking